The
the.
The the.
The you
the.
The
.
I. Got it thank God I'm.
Going to find
a way to die after being thirty first all
of that if I can help it. Looks like.
My. Kind of but I'm not.
Then. That's not true I just wanted
to go didn't we want to cross
our words with this to this well. I think
I know most I mean we were talking and
been short of water
a long time but you were kind.
Of the bit tight with him Troy
keeps prince in there. And. You have
the famous man. Even here in our courts
they tell endless stories of his glorious
but of successful battles. Why don't honor
for us the last great defender of Troy
as we do our land as far as I'm concerned
he's just an intruder good too impulsive
in
a sense you know if famous and
there speak to this pick. I
want to mean. We thank you and I mean you
see we're more generous than the Greeks
were. Some of them tell. Me You know
you. Mean you.
Know.
Where you're cheap. What you want.
So you're. Famous Trojan
warrior he looks just like
a common interest exactly like the rest
of. Excuse me he doesn't know anything of
your fame and you always
places too much importance on
a pier. And you. I am to an outing of
the ruefully I salute our celebrated
visitor and offering any help you may need
on his voyage we don't need your help we
will stay here I've already made our request
to can Latino I'm awaiting the return
of our messenger now since you refuse my
help I beg you at least listen to some
good counsel. Take food and water and get
out of here as quickly as you can that
doesn't sound like Council but more like
an order you must know these lands they
belong to the king of low rent them is the
only one who has the right to tell us to
leave the only one. Take
a good look at your men do you
think they're still able to handle
a spear Why don't you try them.
It's.
Thing
. What are they going to do now I don't
know but I can tell you what we're
going to do over going to
build our hearts and enjoy
a well earned rest. That go back
to work everybody is going to work
all of us come to work.
I better go on to arrest them you go back
to Philly and bring me two companies of
my best wires we don't need
to use your men I know
a way to take care of that or camp
intruders. Over there in the valley or the
pastors of King of Andro full of enormous
bulls run tamed and vicious and savage.
With
a little persuasion the herders will lend
them to us. Well be thrown against you
lease. And we'll even get our hands dirty.
You are happy.
About that. And I. And
I and I got us back where
it comes and it's got
a charm Thank you. It's
got no isn't
a thing Latino was waiting for you on
the run from you'll be welcome with the
respect and honor which protect your
family but mother with hope for all of the
rulers of the neighborhood kingdoms
in this region a lot to mull
a sample tomorrow at the Royal Palace to
greet you they've all been invited there
by Latino. What did you hear
about Joe know. He's the King of
you the nephew clean him up
a bit you treats him like
a funny idea what. Coming up like.
At the minute Senator what.
Kind of like the.
Going to the wrestler.
Hey I have a
a hit hen it
head when.
He has.
Yet.
That's why I asked you about so enough I
thought to do something like this what do
you propose an else. Get an escort
ready. I intend to leave now
with
a friend in the King as long as I'm.
I have to visit him very good you
like broken Yes So that's just
a little haven't asked us that's right.
Of the frame and leave it to Joe isn't it
I'm trusting you with a command
of the cap more logs and build
a high and strong stockade Don't you worry
and I'll take good care of everything.
Julia. Are you afraid of those
both. Well a little maybe. I didn't harm
a good son. I'm leaving
for the ranch and soon.
I ran to get
a chance to talk to one another. And I'm
always watching you. I know. That's how.
I see you organize it truly while gathering
the strangers around. Carried out the
instructions given me by the King after
he admitted just to the most influential
minister the king ever had that the most
Lord. You might be very useful in my
service. You have
a sense. So
your ken has ordered his people
to provide a welcome. But if
a man doesn't appear what makes you think
you will. It's only. You know their
current.
I'm glad you're here I know your
father depends on you but it's
a pity we've had no chance to
see one another yes and it's
a pity I haven't seen you all men
visiting our lands at night stealing our
livestock. Bury our young
friend I'm sorry has
a very sharp tongue I'm surprised you know
very well he's telling the truth he's
not going to greet you like
a brother. You don't really believe all
those lies do. I prefer to believe nothing
at all. Rather than what I hear
you. Well sad that proves you love
me just as much you never did. Perhaps
does it really matter to you.
Matters
a lot more than you know. I
. I.
I. I.
I. Wasn't the start
welcoming to strong on the
contrary I'm boy. Still you can't you
no more beautiful than ever you think
I had
a special these. I. Think
you need an explanation
don't forget Alekhine's to scale it simply
to my duty I try but when I come around
and I'm not
a guest to well. THANK YOU THANK
YOU THANK YOU THANK
YOU
ILY
THANK YOU
THANK YOU al.
And me it's an honor to receive you yeah
present my White Queen I'm out and my
daughter Olivia. It's hard for me to
express my thanks for this welcome.
Your bravery is known to all of us though
you are in exile the glory of Troy lives
in your name our people were driven from
our lands that's why I've come to you
we've heard much about the long and useless
war that destroyed your homeland and
from what we've been told the bank which
behaved more Nobody than the victors. No
words of truth anymore since the glorious
days of peace and dry. Fate has brought
us here to your lad I prefer to look upon
it as the return. Of the founder of Troy
It was
a mob scene race I'm happy this ancient
tie lives in your memory to give me hope
that I request will be granted. Give us
refuge in your life and we've come to the
river Tyree by the will of the gods if
you will out we will stay you have my word
that your request will be considered by
us most big. And I say this on behalf of
the other royal houses were gathered here
today to pay you their due respect I mean
we know all the polls it would be hard to
find a man who rivals or encourage
and. Thank you for having on
a tree with your presence.
This son of Kenya wonders.
If my father were handicapped
by his great A.G.M.
Self would greet you I'm proud to be welcome
he should be proud of his son I would
tell him that. And this is to know King
of the roots. We've already met I had the
pleasure of visiting us cap on my way
here I admire his large band of brave
followers and their leader of course the
illustrious and there. Before I left I
gave
a little advice to I had proof of your
admiration after your god might I be permitted
a servant of the Crown to pay homage to
our celebrated much travel guest cultures
my most faithful ministers.
All the princes taking part in the games
are choosing therefore. You intend to be
there. Left with by the counter only
want to tell you don't allow turning to
provoke your ex what I mean is just
behave with the dignity you should be for
outside. My door comment on the.
What went on You Tube that you can.
Something important to. You know to know
about of them. Why did they want to leave
that for many reasons I suppose surely for
just as many reasons I want you to stay
there for I will use all my influence to
support your request to the king. A great
painter those first those first
some years ago if you wish going
thank God. I'm
a street turn to the king. For
.
I was hoping that you wouldn't discover
this room while cutting. I know it's
a painful feeling to be faced with the
truth of the past our memories can be even
more painful I will remember all of this I
have nothing else to remember I hope you
found at least the painter was impartial
only time is impartial the truth the
stabbers between victors and bank wished
backgrounds and peace are you saying now
that you don't hate your enemies and you
know. They're no longer enemies I fought
them without hating them I find only because
I love what I was defending. But the
Greeks did to Idaho man and send you and
your people and of exile. That's true but
these memories don't create him
bitterness. Or hatred. I never quite
expected you. What to do
expect. I thought you'd
see the empty phrases all heroes you.
Believe only and for an infant. Maybe I'm
not
a girl of course he is living. On
the name is simply being modest
you've seen the warm welcome he gets
from the peasants and townspeople It's
impressive and they're the ones who really
created. Come child I'm sure are famous
is a need of rest it's been
a tiring day even for him thank you for
your courtesy Your hospitality is well
known I've been looking for you
a martyr I'd like to see you too you
and I see far too much of each other
you must have
a little patience to know of any As always
been very headstrong I have been patient
for how much longer until she gets to
know you better realize your qualities we
have no more time why not do you still
hope to see me rain is doing on the throne
of the random of course you my nephew Very
well then you'd better act before the
Trojan steps in ruins our plans.
And. I mean what makes
you think he could be
a threat to us I know what he can do you
are there I'll just let you know hung on
his every word and you saw the people
cheered him you know that we have a code of
a man from always receive I guess Fong any
I'm aware of that and they are however
isn't just another guest men like him think
they're champions of the downtrodden
defenders of liberty they have an uncanny
strength one that gives courage to weaker
men Am I mistaken how you praising him not
at all I'm trying to make you see the
danger to both of us of the remains
here and not see him do you
think you'll be satisfied with
a little plot of land on the Tiber and what
will they ask for later if his prestige
keeps on growing what you say is true in
the steel within and I think I may no way
we can do it Tommy how they'll
forget that Latino hasn't come to
a decision about and yet I can convince
my husband not to grant him the land he
wants you or the king he went too far to
trap refuse and then now perhaps you have
another solution if so what
is it. That I must marry
Lavinia it wants this to be I'm out of
time is working for Annette but there is
hope married to Lavinia I could drive
those Trojan beggars out of Latium
I know how much I'm asking of you but
everything is lost unless your husband
announces we're betrothed doesn't tonight
Levine is my daughter her happiness is
important to me and she doesn't love you
she told me so you'll be could have
promised me you have my promise I know
full well what she feels for me so you can
be sure I'll do all I can to make her
love me and to make her happy let me have
some time to think about.
Six.
That we go after the Trojans this time.
We have the advantage is not there is no
longer necessary I don't agree forces all
of us that's where your mistakes. You
learn to be a little more artful
a little less the tyrant the still beating
of your trust in CSMA Sencion just my
face again and through
Monday if I help you
you.
Poor. Poor.
Old age
and its analysts the if you do the way.
I say we have another thing about
it like the safe return of. Two I
was merely distasteful to
you you need becoming more.
I think things it has no
meaning for you. You have
a right to your feelings. And
whatever they are. Always the same.
When I take a horse charge to fill up
with a job no thank you I'm here as
a spectator. Spectators never one of
the competitions or so I've heard.
I haven't entered this one yet. If I
decide to I'll be sure and let you know.
Those. Your distinguished guests arriving
imagist all right and what if you decided
if my happiness if my wishes still had any
meaning to it I ask you both forget that
our daughter's wishes are also important
that the media will reign with to know she
will have
a strong man on the throne that side one
can make decisions and make them without
the aid of
a counselor who still don't agree with my
policies your policies are weak that's
because you've only been doing the things
that cultures want you to do I hate all
violence and always have. And I believe
the peoples of loves him are able to live
in peace with one another stop being so
unrealistic when Lavinia puts on my crown I
want to be sure she's weighing more than
a piece of jewelry it must be the symbol
of power when you speak like that I think
that your toenails voice and when I listen
to you I hear the words of conscious
what you have against my nephew when you
tell me it would be unwise to give Torah
more power than he has we have to think
of our other neighbors like him you must
know their trust and haters on his account
and since when have you been afraid of
the
a trust ever since I learned that they
have learned their army soldier strong all
of us if we start warming ourselves I'm
not sure which is worse to know what is
friend too then. They think they understand
follow but they're only tired it's not
to turn on
a tyrant he never act like one if you
give in and grab some of. You've got to
announce tonight that you have promised to
him he can marry I don't have any and if
you don't you lose what respect I have
for you my husband won't be needing your
consul any more you are dismissed he's
the king he'll make all the decisions.
Don't worry you'll have
to laugh. Because he.
Kept talking.
Now don't be.
Know. There was lot of big. Push. To put
you in
a I have come to us in good faith to ask
us that which I can give love to human
ready to grant you and your followers with
all of the privileges of Micron I grant
you complete sovereignty over the lands
of joining the folks of the type of
sovereignty which will remain with you
until songs who will bear the rank of
princes of loves you from this day forth
and for old time. Why don't I just do what
I tell you. First.
Try. Your Majesty now I've only words with
which to thank you but I can promise you
this but you'll never regret the gift you
have given the Trojans today you're not
going to take Him at His word are
you like do you know you're making
a serious mistake tearing apart
sorting them to give territory to
a band of foreigners I give you fair warning
this dangerous move which you think
concerns all a lot Jim is certain to put
a great strain on our alliance
in low rent and there's always
a place for those who want to live in peace
and friendship even foreigners but your
country is only one of many and that's him
why not ask US border yours ask us if we
want these people to stay here or not to
me or how do you feel about it I share
with King Latino his
respect for the N.A.S.
But my basic position remains unchanged I
do agree with two of them no not that I
dispute your right to grant you don't want
to anyone you choose but I do take into
account the possible risks the consequences
of this foreign invasion. We all
welcome you among us and I are those of us
who love peace and justice rejoice that
you are now
a prince equal in power to all of lot cm's
rulers we too have been forced to submit
to abuses been humiliated as you were
a Troy I don't wish to maintain constantly
that the only valid rule is the law of
Iowans No let's call it force let
no one say it isn't useful I use it
whenever necessary and I always get the
best results apply your non-routine Leah as
long as you can but in my lands now that
mine only just laws are valid and no
one will break them no one. Hears it.
And then what it was
a word with you. Just
. You can spare yourself
the trouble I've already
seen this room are you quite
sure. On the contrary I have the
impression you completely forgotten
what happens to those who oppose
a power greater than their own. Dignity
no is granted you the lands you want
you receive the approval of the crowds but
you need more you may not think so but
it's most important you need my
approval I can do without it. That's
a hard thing to do you're in my way
you know and I kind of allow that.
I'm telling you for the last time. I
leave here you think you can drive me
away and you think you're going to oppose
me and then. I don't accept the king's
decision I'll fight it with all my
strength something else to say I don't
take what I offer you food wagons and gold
leave peacefully and then your voyage
listen to me and the goes tomorrow I can
guarantee you anything not even your life
and now you listen to me we're staying on
the land that was given us at any cost
you're staying on the land
above which are under. Most
impressive that Trojan
horse. Until tomorrow
been so glad to see him.
I think you do yours in the finest possible
your cap my friends why you put up the
stockade we have to be ready to take care
of many uninvited guys have enrolled
while the cattle driven to newsmen. All
right go ahead and tell us where is all
that game you say will buy your biographies
of the city there are deer wild there
and rabbits you show us where I take care
of these fields along the Tiber and I
must leave them but if you follow my
directions you'll get there without any
problem. When you need the caps just go
along the stream until you come to the
white rocks there's some poplars just
to the left of them after that there's
a great hope for so you'll find all the
deer you can possibly want like give us all
this information Shepherd What do you
want from us and to whom you keep all the
meat I'd like you to give me to hide
everything you kill burn up ready for the hunt
and.
The do you want to go along without trying
to be good. So far you've got to pull on
the boat's crew. Takes more than
a you've got to draw the boat straight all
the way to your shoulder keep rolling
right now you can get through
with one shot after. Shot.
All the way you got over it
back again and you'd better get
a move on it pretty so again it's not quite
the get back you'll go to bed hungry.
You know where
Holroyd
old
. All right if you.
Stay.
I give you this billed as a symbol
of your factory but surely not as
a. Victory you will know
you did not matter.
I.
Very well that I challenge everyone I'm
home and willing to give this phone to
anyone here who can do that and I.
Accept that challenge.
Oh OK.
Your Majesty with your permission I would
like to give this. Is really the one who
deserves.
The structures OK.
OK. OK OK OK.
I'll you do it. Why are you interrupting
the gig. This can't wait two of your loyal
subjects have been brutally killed only
because they were trying to uphold the
sacred laws of momentum.
All of you here knew the priest hero
the guardian of the segment year.
I just fun factor lol. Now. I'm
in hell prison. Because they are the
ones responsible for killing our beloved
priest. Because this
group no one told us the year was sacred
our people need food we were told we could
come when we want. He wants to
know who killed his kid I wanted.
Him hiding in the woods with. The family
they jumped out of the musta been more
than thirty and so me did you kill those
men we tried our best not we thought they
were torturing without mercy
they would have killed
a solid if we had one that. Way
. You heard them. You
know the procedure what.
People don't thing that people give
me time to find out the truth.
No. Just.
Beginning to believe. It was necessary.
To go.
The way I look
a any. Thing I want.
Eh. Let.
Em.
At least
a bit. To get. Her. To
get.
Her up to pay.
A.
Little earlier but we've got to get to the
east gate immediately before they block
every way out of the city there are more
of my men out there with horses brawling
you know if I must speak to Latino First
I have to prove to them the Trojans are
not at fault time don't give you time
for that little city's on its side.
Go out that way quickly. What are you going
to do to protect you know don't worry
about me you must think you're going above.
And save yourself and you know you're
the only hope we have now.
I must go back to camp before total attacks
I don't think you leave Loretta before
tomorrow he needs
a time to organize his army and prepare
for an assault I can't risk it if you tax
I've got to be there with my people blocked
you go talk with the atrocities they
will join forces with us yes they want to
be glad to help us because to know what
my stance you will be
a menace to them too I know but the
atrocities are suspicious of me because I was
once thought it was right it won't be easy
to convince the now that I'm no longer
an ally of Italy but I'll drop it if
I have any luck I'll rejoin you with
a large force of
a trust in the rest of my own I get on
will go with you. If you're on able to win
them over send them back to camp by
sundown if you want your mail all me.
I am.
It's impossible I can't do it to us. I
have no doubt that India will end up with
a guilty man if there's any truth in what
sense you say you mean you're still in
this despite the fact that it is fed with
his accomplices if he's innocent let him
come prove it and face being stoned to death
by an angry crowd the hatred you many
times is beyond all control the body of
that priest lying down there in the square
with his son speaks much more eloquently
than anything you're saying it was
a trap the trying to defend them from.
Really not against me and my man the people
want justice and they demand it now. Listen
to them if you know their voice is more
powerful than yours but you have no cause
to tonal atonement and betray if it was
a name your new ally. There's no need
to look for couches killed you think
a little Minister but maybe it was all
for the best Now I won't be able to
influence you with all that poisonous chatter
which made you nothing more than his
royal palm none of which
other but if the only way
a man like and there could be so faithless
is to renounce his oath of loyalty when
he's always talked about peace he came
here to West for hospitality and he was
given of course and he's taking the
best advantage of it and they want
a lot more now that we've uncovered
a deceitful attack as I'm sure of that
we should level at Camp Bernard to the
ground there's no other way and you know
as well as I do you must wait wait before
the blood is spilled for nothing we might
be able to wait but the people won't. Ask
you to open the temple of the war god if
you now fail to attack the Trojans your
people will rebel against. My soldiers
going to be if they're told to stop the
riots which have started why ask me that
why not ask. The commander of forces.
All of your soldiers agree with the people
and the people demand that the priest
your own and young sons will be avenged.
You will defend the random defend your phone
as well as already gone to collect my
soldiers we have been ill or army I'm afraid
you're mistaken why should I join you
in this insane venture. Is that what you
call it. It seems to me that yesterday you
agreed with my ideas let's clarify your
ideas you hate and they are and because of
that you want us all to risk
a costly war with your Tuscans. We
must liberate those lands on the Tiber and
drive me out your soldiers in mind leave
your track of where Camilla will come to
a sense of the she cares for me what is
it you want. That you open the temple of
justice. That the pool is the
one who wants this war. The
responsibility is alone. And I accept it
yes all responsibility Bush and they have
the custodians the power the ceremony.
Let us go live in your.
They are. There.
You know.
How many of you made up two hundred all
good and strong and I wondered if you last
get some of those stories done as old men
do and we'll be able to use them better
than most of these young ghettos you're
going after way to some of us young devils
have no use for this on and
maybe I'll get one. Of.
The men I come up and going up courage
Let's hope that I get I'm coming back soon
with good news. Let's hope so but it's
already sunset and there's no sign of him
all the trust going. Where we can be grateful
no one seemed to and I don't believe
we can risk leaving the room too much
before tomorrow. Throughout the week.
To money from the break right through
on the first of. Everyone take cover
everybody but the soldiers.
I don't think they'll attack us now in
a short while it'll be dark Turner
has come to show us his power.
For your pea pod Trafton leave the. But
I think your laugh Barney you come.
On down you'll be slaughtered
every one have you.
And I'll come and take back. With you
if I can. Open the gates.
Oh yeah.
We mustn't delude ourselves any longer to
try to resist or to help would be suicide
I must make my way through his lines I
must bring back our total destroyers
tomorrow Blondie cannot have been able to
convince the address can I maybe I won't
be but it's my duty to try if I were to
stay here the only thing I could do would
be to open the gates and big toto to spare
our women and children go and every one
of us knows that if the interest comes we'll
listen to any man as you. The trouble
of making your way down as winds as strong
you need someone to go along with you
please let me come to I want to get ready.
No more.
Let's go free and I know horses
there. Is no time at all.
It's.
Well. You could be
a. Half
.
Or were were you are or were
you are
or were.
The BE.
To.
The. KING.
KING.
Cake.
Walk. We need many as you can.
Hear Furthermore all we need more.
You get your man and pretend you're talking
Turner's cavalry. The last moment right
through into the woods over there to the
right of him can. Be sure to follow. Our
Way to one side that would then with the
oppressed can drop off fall upon those who
still remain in front of the
cap gun on me. That's got.
Her. The owner go.
Undergo.
They are.
Out as police come.
Ere
.
S.
Elite.
F.
.
S.
. It's the messenger we've been waiting
for. For Not couple responded Polanski's
minute to the words that's
just what we wanted.
Through Texas. I was afraid this rare.
Our defense Mark. What.
It.
Is that's coming up this.
Thank you. Keep. Going to
Q. Q.
Q A and.
What do you do we get some.
Theory. That you're walking.
Right. Every. TIME You
look gorgeous with the
force of. The slaughter of the bush
and they all run away with me like.
Nowadays attacking our soldiers on the cap
if we stay here will be destroyed. For
them feel comfortable to be able to keep
an. Eye Lowenthal have to defend the city
. And I am.
I. Going to.
I.
Think.
Have his body put on
a watch and it's going to
his home. On his own. And
I've worn that. As if you were my brother.
We're.
Coming.
Oh.
Too many dead. What good is this truce
of tomorrow the killing begins all over
again.
Only during the week
a week to eat.
Eat
anything and wait there.
Why have you come here. To speak to your
father you must listen to me. What can he
do you know he didn't want this war I know
but he can help me ended before it's too
late how can he help tell me
what is it you have to say.
To the Trojans I've been accused of provoking
this war and I've never been allowed
the chance to disprove it. However you
surely must realize that the truth can no
longer be at the does accusation against
is that all of the prejudice and hatred
spread among our peoples come from the
ambitions of just one man today after
helping us win our victory in the field
their trust in our Me was ready to march
directly on Laurent M I restrain them but
tomorrow if you continue to fight I won't
be able to stop them will defend ourselves
you from Troy know better than any of us
how long a city can hold out
against the sea but we had
a just cause the people believed in it
they knew why they were fighting look at
these people how long will they go on
fighting to support your cause your ambition
. What are you asking me to do surrender
low rent to. Know I've come here to
offer myself in the cause of peace.
If too and I will do the same that combat
between the two of us alone decide the
outcome of this terrible war if I am
defeated I have the address comes promise to
withdraw together with the Trojans alone
to say that you kill me what is there to
stop you from taking over the phone of
a ransom I shall lay my weapons
at the feet of the King as
a token of friendship and respect.
Some of us here have doubted you but this
is the best proof of your good faith and
the honor of your countrymen.
Very well tomorrow I'll be at the
gates of your camp prepare yourself trojan
for it will be your last day on earth.
Thank you
thank
.
You. Larry. The
auxiliary.
I'm here because I wanted to be with you
with time you should give compliments I
had to come I couldn't bear the thought of
not seeing you would you please go back
or in the matter what your father or protector
What does it matter to me where I am
if you hadn't come. For the
thought that I might do for
a friend to. Keep
me. I know how foolish you think I am
but I'm in love with. You way this
week here I come here with the kids to
stay I don't ever want to let you go.
Every.
Other. One of the year
it's turned out. OK.
Yes if you like we do can
we together and becomes.
The you.
Open the gate.
If you.
I am. I
am. I am.
I am.
I am. I
am. I am
am. I
.
She.
Her.
If the story of an in. The lifetime of one
man is linked to the most exciting of
legendary event the fall of Troy and the
birth of rope. And his robe he grows
through the centuries legend is slowly
transformed into this. History of civil war
expansion into empire finally the
beginnings of oh Western civilization.